Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): Well it's a beautiful day in Stillwater, a little windy, a little crisp, but it's absolutely gorgeous and I love coming to Stillwater and I'm here with, well all my mayors in the 4th district are my favorite, but I'm here with Mayor Ted of Stillwater right now. So should
I
Speaker 2: come to Stillwater this weekend?
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Absolutely. Congresswoman, we're hosting the fishing opener. The first time in the history of the Minnesota fishing opener that the city of Stillwater, the birthplace of Minnesota, is hosting it and it's going to be a magical weekend. The weather looks like it's going to be beautiful. We've
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): We've got great music, live music, food, all sorts of fun stuff to do even if you're not interested in getting on the water for the opener. It's going to be a beautiful weekend in town.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): Well, I love coming to Stillwater anytime, but this weekend will be very, very special.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): It's going to be great. I wouldn't miss
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): it. Alright, so get down to Stillwater. The sooner the better.
Get
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): your fishing license. Come on and see us.